A Guide to the Repass-Umberger Family Papers, 1819-1968
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Repass-Umberger Family Papers 1819-1968
Special Collections, Kegley Library
2004.5
25 folders; 124 photographs.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Margaret Cobb Wampler in 2004.
Biographical Information
The son of William Repass and Barbara Harkrader, Gordon Repass was born on 12 January 1819 in Black Lick in the western portion of Wythe County, Virginia. He married Anna Magdalena Sharitz, daughter of Daniel Sharitz and Mary Sluss Sharitz on 21 March 1839. Anna Sharitz was born on 12 February 1819. The couple had ten children as follows: Elmira J. Repass (1839-1841), Reuben F. Repass (1841-1922), Richard T. Repass (1844-1858), Mary E. Repass (1846-1869), Emily V. Repass (1848-1924), Selden W. L. Repass (1850-1929), unnamed infant (1852), Clementina E. Repass (1854-1862), Margaret B. Repass (1857-1937), and Ella G. Repass (1864-1944).
Like generations before him, Gordon Repass farmed the fertile soil of Black Lick. When Civil War erupted, he was forty-two and did not expect to serve in the Confederate Army as did his son, Reuben, who enlisted in the 8th Virginia Cavalry Regiment in 1861. Gordon joined the home guards (4th Regiment, Virginia Reserves) early in the conflict. However, Confederate military authorities sent Repass to join the 1st Virginia Infantry Regiment in the trenches around Richmond late in 1864. In his letters home to Anna, he writes about his futile attempts to be discharged from this regiment or to be reassigned to the home defense guard or reserve units. Captured by Federal soldiers on 6 April 1865 near Farmville, Repass died of dysentery at Point Lookout Prison, Maryland, on 3 May 1865. He is buried at the prison. Anna Sharitz Repass never remarried, raising her children and managing the farm by herself. She died on 7 March 1899.
His son, Reuben F. Repass, survived the war and married Ellen Missouri Brown on 25 April 1865. In 1869, Reuben and Ellen, with their children Lee Gordon and Laura Edna, moved to Missouri where they lived until 1876 when they relocated to Texas. His wife Ellen died on 14 August 1904 and he later married Lizzie Wright. Reuben died in Graham, Texas on 1 August 1922.
Margaret B. Repass married Stephen A. Umberger on 5 November 1877. They had the following children: Chloe A. Umberger (1878-1939; married Walter Spence), Gordon Repass Umberger (1880-1945), Lois E. Umberger (1882-1974), Anna K. Umberger (1883-1933), Virginia A. Umberger (1885-1953; married Frank Repass Brown), infant son (1893), and Margaret Belle Umberger (b. 1894; married Edgar Cobb). Margaret B. Repass Umberger died on 10 January 1937 and Stephen A. Umberger died on 15 December 1924.
Selden W. L. Repass married 1) Elizabeth Florence Earhart (1848-1893) by whom he had a daughter, Olive Anna Repass (married Walter B. Brown); 2) Lula Mae Umberger Repass (1868-1898); 3) Ella B. Patterson (1867-1938). Selden Repass died on 3 June 1929.
Scope and Content
Series I, Correspondence (1862-1920, undated), contains letters sent by Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass and their family during the Civil War. Repass, conscripted into the 1st Virginia Infantry Regiment, C. S. A. in 1864, spent his service in the defenses around Richmond, Virginia. Captured in April 1865, he died at Point Lookout prison in Maryland on 3 May 1865 from dysentery. Photocopies of letters written by his son Reuben F. Repass, who moved to Texas after the Civil War, are also included in this series as is correspondence of other family members.
Series II, Financial Records (1847-1925, undated), is comprised of two account books, promissory notes, receipts, and tax tickets. One account book, dating 1847 to 1899, contains financial transactions by Gordon Repass, Anna Sharitz Repass, and Selden W. L. Repass and an inventory of Gordon Repass' estate. A letter from Selden W. L. Repass to Reuben F. Repass is also in the book. The other account book, kept by Anna Sharitz Repass from 1858 to 1880, is comprised of financial transactions and a memoir by Reuben F. Repass The Campaign of 1861. This account book also has various notes on family history and vital records. Photocopies of many of these records have been placed in the Kegley Library files.
Series III, Legal Records (1849-1904), contains deeds between Gordon Repass, Selden W. L. Repass, Reuben F. Repass, Stephen A. Umberger and others. Also included in this series are records pertaining to the estate of Anna Magdalena Sharitz Repass who died on 7 March 1899.
Series IV, Genealogical Records (1819-1968, undated), contains a wealth of family history information collected by Anna Sharitz Repass and her granddaughters, Lois Ella Umberger and Margaret Belle Umberger Cobb. Specifically, this series contains four memorandum books kept by Anna Sharitz Repass in which she recorded daily events and weather. Other material includes obituaries and research notes on the Repass, Umberger, Sharitz, Doak, Howe and Huddle families as well as photocopies of records from the Bible of Gordon Repass. Correspondence and research notes of Lois E. Umberger and Margaret Bell Umberger Cobb (descendants of Gordon Repass and Stephen A. Umberger) regarding Umberger family history are also in this series. A photograph of the 1819 fraktur (baptismal certificate) of Anna Sharitz Repass is also in this series. Photocopies of many of these records have been placed in the Kegley Library vertical files.
Series V, Miscellaneous Records (1845-1908, undated), includes records of Marvin Methodist Church and the Black Lick Farmers Club as well as literary manuscripts by Maggie B. Repass Umberger and others.
Series VI, Photographs, contains 124 photographs (sepia, black and white, and ferrotypes) of members of the Brown, Cobb, Cox, King, Minter, Repass, Sharitz, Spence, Topham and Umberger families.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Gose, George B. Pioneers of the Virginia Bluegrass. Radford, VA: Commonwealth Press, 1971.
Hoch, Beverly Repass. The Civil War Journal and Letters of Reuben F. Repass. Wythe County Historical Review. 58. July 2000: 1-12.
Hoch, Beverly Repass. From Ziefen to Sally Run: Swiss Pioneer Jacob Repass (1734-1814) on the American Frontier. Albuquerque, NM: Jacob Repass Memorial Fund, 1993.
Umberger, Arthur D. Umberger (Umbarger) Family Chart. Aldan, PA.: Umberger, 1981.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence. 1862-1920, undated., 8 folders.
  - Folder 1. Correspondence - Gordon Repass. 1862, 1864., 7 items. (Folder 1)
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. 31 March 1862., 1 p.; pen. (Folder-item 1:1)
      He requests her prayers during his time of military service and asks her to guide their children's religious training.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Camp Lee, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 6 November 1864., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 1:2)
      he writes about his new assignment to the 1st Virginia Infantry Regiment encamped near Richmond, Virginia.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 13 November 1864., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 1:3)
      He writes about his mess-mates J. P. Sharitz, Alfred Catron, John Thomas and Michael Thomas, picket duty, church services in camp, and instructions for hog butchering.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 20 November 1864., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 1:4)
      He writes about his camp meals and cooking, skirmish with enemy, and religious life.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 27 November 1864., 4 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 1:5)
      He writes from Camp Duns, 4 miles southeast of Chester Station in the trenches, about illnesses of A. Hines, J. P. Sharitz, and William Kegley, his failed attempts to get reassigned, camp rations, and instructions for harvest.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 12 December 1864, 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 1:6)
      he writes regarding his illness, picket duty, attempts to get him home, and hog butchering instructions.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 30 December 1864., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 1:7)
      He comments on her description of Yankee raid into Wythe County [Stoneman's raid], his picket duty, and her stolen horse.
  - Folder 2. Correspondence - Gordon Repass. January - February 1865., 9 items. (Folder 2)
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 2 January 1865., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:1)
      He writes about his rheumatism, official denial of his request for discharge from Robert E. Lee, his desire to be reassigned to reserve forces, and his intention to seek counsel from an attorney and issue of writ of habeas corpus.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 7 January 1865., 4 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:2)
      He writes about his illness (probably dysentery), picket duty, thrashing of grain, his hunger, prayer meeting in camp, his clothing and laundry chores, and wounding of their son Reuben Repass.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. 8, 9 January 1865., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:3)
      He writes about his lack of food and hunger and new position near the James River.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. 3 February 1865., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:4)
      He writes about his failed efforts to get reassigned to the reserve forces because he was not forty-five when he was conscripted. He also requests a box of provisions from home including meat, bread, cornmeal, flour, beans, fruit, and soap. On reverse: Reuben Repass, Wytheville, Virginia to Gordon Repass. 18 January 1865. 1 p.; pen. He encloses certificate of his father's age from court records.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 12 February 1865., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item. 2:5)
      He writes about his rheumatism, his stomach and head pains, high cost of food, and his beliefs that the Confederacy will not last because of lack of grain.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. [12 February 1865]., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:6)
      He wishes her a happy birthday and gives instructions and messages to his children.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 16 February 1865., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:7)
      He writes about his recovery from yellow jaundice an the again requests a box of provisions.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass and Reuben Repass. 20 February 1865., 4 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 2:8)
      He writes about his rheumatism, low rations, and high prices for provisions. He inquiries about payment of the tax-in-kind in grain, provides instructions for farming, and mentions deserters.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Camp Howlett, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass and Reuben Repass. 23 February 1865., 2 p.; pencil; faded. (Folder-item 2:9)
      He writes about his bad health.
  - Folder 3. Correspondence - Gordon Repass. March - June 1865., 7 items. (Folder 3)
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 6 March 1865., 2 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 3:1)
      He writes about his regiment's relocation to Duns Farm and the possibility of movement to Petersburg, receipt of the box of provisions, and his continued strategy to get reassigned to the reserve forces.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia, in the trenches below Richmond, to Anna Sharitz Repass. 20 March 1865., 4 p.; pencil; torn. (Folder-item 3:2)
      He describes the constant marching of the regiment and his failed efforts to get reassigned.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Henrico County, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 24 March 1865., 4 p.; pencil. (Folder-item 3:3)
      He writes about constant marching and his meeting with their son, Reuben F. Repass who adds a note, dated 25 March 1865.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Chesterfield County, Virginia, encamped 2 miles northeast of Petersburg, to Anna Sharitz Repass. 29 March 1865., 3 p.; pencil; faded; torn. (Folder-item 3:4)
      He writes about his dashed hopes of ever getting reassigned to reserve forces.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass, Point Lookout Prison Camp, Maryland to Selden W. L. Repass. 9 April 1865., 2 p.; pencil; faded. (Folder-item 3:5)
      He urges his children to obey their mother and not neglect their education. Transcription by Beverly Repass Hoch included.
    - John P. Sharitz, Point Lookout, Maryland to Anna Sharitz Repass. 10 May 1865., 4 p.; pen. (Folder-item. 3:6)
      He informs her that Gordon Repass died from chronic dysentery.
    - Letter. V. I. Heintz, Assistant Adjutant General, Office Commissary General of Prisoners, Washington, D. C. to R. F. Repass, Wytheville, Virginia. 12 June 1865., 1 p. (Folder-item. 3:7)
      He informs him that Gordon Repass died on 4 May 1865 at Point Lookout, Maryland from chronic dysentery.
  - Folder 4. Correspondence - Gordon Repass. Undated., 9 items. (Folder 4)
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 1 p.; pencil. (Folder-item. 4:1)
      He complains that there is no chance for a man to get justice in this part of the army.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 1 p.; pencil; fragment. (Folder 4:2)
      He requests peaches and thread.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 2 p.; pencil; fragment. (Folder-item 4:3)
      He gives recommendations for farming.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 2 p.; pencil; fragment. (Folder-item. 4:4)
      He gives instructions for sending box of provisions.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 1 p.; pencil; fragment. (Folder-item 4:5)
      He discusses foods he misses eating with his family.
    - Letter. Gordon Repass to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 2 p.; pen; fragment. (Folder-item. 4:6)
      He writes about box of provisions and attempts to be reassigned to reserve forces.
    - Envelope addressed to Mrs. A. M. Repass, Rural Retreat, Virginia. Undated. (Folder-item. 4:7)
    - Envelope addressed to Mr. Gordon Repass, Co. K, 1st Virginia Infantry, Terry's Brigade, Pickett's Division, Army Northern Virginia, Richmond, Virginia. Undated. (Folder-item 4:8)
    - Scrap of paper with address of Gordon Repass. Undated. (Folder-item 4:9)
  - Folder 5. Correspondence - Gordon Repass - Transcripts and Notes. (Folder 5)
    Typed transcripts of letters written by Gordon Repass and notes on a exhibit prepared for the Wythe County Historical Society.
  - Folder 6. Correspondence - Reuben Repass - Photocopies. 1869-1920, undated., 10 items. (Folder 6)
    Photocopies of letters written by Reuben Repass, son of Gordon Repass and Anna Sharitz Repass. The original letters are in a private collection.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Rose Hill, Missouri to Anna Sharitz Repass. 17 October 1869., 4 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:1)
      He writes about family illness and farming, His wife, Ellen Missouri Brown Repass, writes to Mary Repass.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Rose Hill, Missouri to Anna Sharitz Repass. 13 January 1870., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:2)
      He writes about death of Mary Repass.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Rose Hill, Missouri to Emily V. Repass. 22 May 1870., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:3)
      He writes about farming and the type of settlers wanted in Missouri. His wife, Ellen Missouri Brown Repass adds a brief note.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, South Prairie, Texas to Anna Sharitz Repass. 22 January 1884., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:4)
      He writes about farming and plans to build a house.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Victor, Colorado to "Dear Sister." 25 May 1905., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:5)
      He writes about his visit to his son Lee Gordon Repass, mining, and describes the town of Victor.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Ivan, Texas to "Dear Sister." 7 November 1917., 3 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:6)
      He writes about his health, World War I, and farming.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Ivan, Texas to "Dear Sister." 27 October 1918., 3 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:7)
      He writes about his grandchildren, Ellen Kennedy, Lee Repass, and Fred Kennedy, weather, oil exploration, and World War II.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Ivan, Texas to "Dear Sister." 13 August 1920., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:8)
      He writes about his vertigo and deafness and farming.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, Graham, Texas to "Dear Sister." 5 October 1920., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:9)
      He writes about leasing his land to oil companies and his family.
    - Poem. Undated., 2 p.; photocopy. (Folder-item. 6:10)
      Poem written by Reuben F. Repass to his sisters during the Civil War, An Answer to Do They Miss Me at Home.
  - Folder 7. Correspondence - Miscellaneous. 1849-1877., 6 items. (Folder 7)
    - Letter. Stephen A. Sharitz, McMinn County, Tennessee to Gordon Repass, Black Lick, Wythe County, Virginia. 8 October 1849., 4 p.; pen.; transcription included. (Folder-item. 7:1)
      He writes about Gordon Repass' conversion to Christianity and farming.
    - Letter. Emma Repass, Wythe County, Virginia to [unknown] Harkrader. 16 August 1865., 2 p.; pen. (Folder-item. 7:2)
      She refuses his attentions speaking plainly and deliberately upon the subject.
    - Letter. Scott & Bolling Company, Richmond, Virginia to Anna Sharitz Repass. 25 November 1869., 1 p.; pen; transcription included. (Folder-item. 7:3)
      They write regarding sales of butter.
    - Letter. A. Marco Davis to Margaret Repass, Black Lick, Wythe County, Virginia. 28 December 1875., 1 p.; pen; envelope. (Folder-item. 7:4)
      He inquires if he could escort her to Macedonia Church next Sunday.
    - Letter. R. Sharitz, Neosha Falls, Woodson County, Kansas to Anna Sharitz Repass. 26 December 1875., 4 p.; pen; torn; transcription included. (Folder-item. 7:5)
      He writes about family of George Shannon, his family, cost of livestock, and his health.
    - Letter. Ella G. Repass to Margaret B. Repass Umberger, Wytheville, Virginia. 2 December 1877., 2 p.; pencil; envelope; transcription included. (Folder-item. 7:6)
      She requests that she bring pieces from her navy blue dress so she can fix her basque.
  - Folder 8. Correspondence - Miscellaneous. 1885-1903, undated., 13 items. (Folder. 8)
    - Letter. Anna Sharitz Repass, Black Lick, Virginia to Emily V. Repass. 15 January 1885., 2 p.; pencil; transcription. (Folder-item. 8:1)
      She writes about her health, illness of various neighbors, and death of Mr. Crowgie.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, South Prairie, Texas to Stephen Umberger. 23 December 1899., 1 p.; pencil. (Folder-item. 8:2)
      He writes about family and farming.
    - Letter. Reuben F. Repass, South Prairie, Texas to S. A. Umberger and Maggie Repass Umberger. 23 December 1899., 1 p.; pen; envelope. (Folder-item. 8:3)
      Receipt for $64.26 for settlement of estate of Anna Sharitz Repass.
    - Letter. Stephen Neel Umberger to Lois Umberger. 1903., 1 p.; typed. (Folder-item. 8:4)
      Written when he was seven years old.
    - Ella Repass Umberger, Oakland, Maryland to Margaret Repass Umberger, Rural Retreat, Virginia. Undated., 8 p.; pen. (Folder-item. 8:5)
      She writes about weather, chickens, family, and church functions.
    - Letter. [unknown] to Lois Umberger and Anna Umberger. Undated., 1 p.; pencil. (Folder-item. 8:6)
      Writer thanks them for Bible.
    - Letter. F. Davis to Anna Sharitz Repass. Undated., 1 p.; pen. (Folder-item. 8:7)
      Davis thanks her for apples.
    - Oath of Allegiance to United States by Anna M. Sharitz Repass. 13 November 1865. (Folder-item. 8:8)
    - Four envelopes. Undated. (Folder-item. 8:9)
- Series II. Financial Records. 1847-1925, Undated., 4 folders.
  - Folder 1. Financial Records - Account Book. 1847-1899., 1 account book; 129 leaves, 260 p.
    Account book used by Gordon Repass, Anna Sharitz Repass, and Selden W. L. Repass from 1847 to 1879 and 1898 to 1899. The book records transactions between the Repass family and neighbors revolving around home work and farming. Included also are notes on the funeral of Anna Sharitz Repass, inventory of the estate of Gordon Repass dated 27 November 1865, and copy of letter by Selden W. L. Repass to Reuben Repass.
  - Folder 2. Account Book of Anna Sharitz Repass. 1858-1880., 1 account book; 59 leaves, 118 p.
    This account book, used by Anna Sharitz Repass, Reuben Repass, and others, contains financial transactions from 1858 to 1899, family notes, and a Civil War memoir by Reuben Repass entitled, The Campaign of 1861.
  - Folder 3. Financial Records - Promissory Notes and Receipts. 1847-1925, undated., 14 items.
    This folder contains 1847 promissory notes from William Repass and Jonathan Repass to Joseph Fisher; 1846-1847 promissory notes from Gordon Repass to William Repass; 1849 promissory note from Gordon Repass to W. B. Winton; 1849 promissory notes from Gordon Repass to William Repass; 1856 statement of Gordon Repass in account with William W. Hedrick; 1857-1858 statement of Gordon Repass in account with William Gibboney; 1857 statement to Gordon Repass in account with John Buchanan and Company; 1862 receipt from W. P. Haller to Gordon Repass; 1869 promissory notes of Anna M. repass, administrator of Gordon Repass' estate, to John P. Sharitz; 1879 account statement of William Repass; undated inventory of Maggie REpass Umberger and Emily Repass Brown; undated bill of work for Gordon Repass; and 1925 receipt from Lindsey & Killinger funeral home for funeral of Stephen Umberger.
  - Folder 4. Financial Records - Tax Tickets. 1854-1882., 7 items.
    This folder contains tax tickets as follows: Wythe County and Virginia state tax for Gordon Repass, 1854; Wythe County and Virginia state tax for Gordon Repass, 1860; Wythe County tax for A. M. Repass, 1882; Wythe County tax for Ella G. Repass, 1881, 1882; Wythe COunty tax for Selden W. L. Repass, 1882; and Wythe County tax for Maggie B. Repass, Umberger, 1881.
- Series III. Legal Records. 1849-1904, 3 folders.
  - Folder 1. Legal Records - Deeds. 1849-1877., 5 items.
    This folder contains deeds as follows: 16 November 1849 between Wiley B. Winton and Sophia Winton and Gordon Repass; 17 July 1877 between Reuben F. Repass and Ellen M. Repass of Texas and Selden W. L. Repass of Virginia; 4 December 1877 between F. S. Blair, Commissioner of the Circuit Court of Wythe County, in the chancery suit of M. D. Brown and wife vs. Reuben Repass and Maggie B. Repass re: real estate of Gordon Repass; 4 December 1877 between F. S. Blair, Commissioner of the Circuit Court of Wythe County, in the chancery suit of M. D. Brown and Reuben Repass and Selden W. L. Repass re: the real estate of Gordon Repass.
  - Folder 2. Legal Records - Deeds. 1883-1904., 4 items.
    This folder contains deeds as follows: 29 August 1883 between Selden W. L. Repass and E. F. Repass and Stephen A. Umberger; 12 December 1883 between Reuben F. Repass and Ellen M. Repass of Texas and Stephen A. Umberger; 14 February 1885 between Edly Doak, John C. Brown, William F. Cloyd, and Canaro D. Doak of one part and Stephen A. Umberger of the other part re: old Macedonia Church property; 1 September 1904 between Ella G. Repass Umberger and J. B. Umberger of Ohio and Maggie B. Umberger.
  - Folder 3. Legal Records - Estate of Anna Sharitz Repass. 1899., 10 items.